
NOM
    C:\Temp\IISWebStats.ps1
    
RÉSUMÉ
    Extract and Concatenate IIS Web or FTP logs locally on a server.
    
    
SYNTAXE
    C:\Temp\IISWebStats.ps1 [[-LogType] <String>] [[-SinceLast] <Int32>] [[-OutFile] <String>] [<CommonParameters>]
    
    C:\Temp\IISWebStats.ps1 [-LogPath] <String> [[-SinceLast] <Int32>] [[-OutFile] <String>] [<CommonParameters>]
    
    
DESCRIPTION
    Locally get IIS Web or FTP logs from a server (It can be used when 
    server have Windows Powershell installed).
    Concatenation of Ms IIS Web or FTP logs for analysis of IIS usage.
    Simplifying URL to only applications root, only by Date, URL, Username
    and Client IP address, and removing of duplicates.
    
    This script need some user interactions and can not be run in a simple
    command line.
    

PARAMÈTRES
    -LogType <String>
        This parameter is only used when no logs path (LogPath) is provided:
        the script will then look for default IIS logs locations:
           C:\inetput\logs\LogFiles
             or
           C:\Windows\system32\LogFiles
        Type of log the script should search for (when LogPath parameter is
        not provided): W3 for Web IIS log directories (W3SVC*) or FTP for FTP
        IIS log directories (MSFTPSVC* or FTPSVC*)
        
        Obligatoire ?                false
        Position ?                   1
        Valeur par défaut                     W3
        Accepter l'entrée de pipeline ?       false
        Accepter les caractères génériques ?  false
        
    -LogPath <String>
        Path of a directory containing Microsoft IIS log files (only *.log files)
        or
        Path of a log file (no file extension limitations), but content should be
        a IIS log file format (see notes).
        
        Obligatoire ?                true
        Position ?                   1
        Valeur par défaut                     
        Accepter l'entrée de pipeline ?       false
        Accepter les caractères génériques ?  false
        
    -SinceLast <Int32>
        Number of logs history to process. By default, the script will process
        on all found log files. This parameter let you limit the script to only
        process logs from 1 to 12 last months. It always get logs from 1st day of
        the last define months (by running script on 15th December and with this
        parameter defined to 3, the script will process all log files created 
        between 1st September and 15th December).
        
        Obligatoire ?                false
        Position ?                   2
        Valeur par défaut                     0
        Accepter l'entrée de pipeline ?       false
        Accepter les caractères génériques ?  false
        
    -OutFile <String>
        Path of a directory where script will save its results (he script will
        automatically generate output file name)
        or
        Path of an output file name.
        This path should be asbolute path.
        If this parameter is ignored then script will save its results in its
        location and automatically generate the file name.
        The Default file name is:
        <W3|FTP|Custom>_logs_export-<ALL|L01-L12>-<yyyyMMdd-HHmm_ss>.txt
          Examples:
            W3_logs_export-All-20180115-1055_38.txt
            FTP_logs_export-L06-20180116-0912_19.txt
        
        Obligatoire ?                false
        Position ?                   3
        Valeur par défaut                     
        Accepter l'entrée de pipeline ?       false
        Accepter les caractères génériques ?  false
        
    <CommonParameters>
        Cette applet de commande prend en charge les paramètres courants : Verbose, Debug,
     ErrorAction, ErrorVariable, WarningAction, WarningVariable,
     OutBuffer, PipelineVariable et OutVariable. Pour plus d’informations, voir
     about_CommonParameters (http://go.microsoft.com/fwlink/?LinkID=113216). 
    
ENTRÉES
    None. You cannot pipe objects to IISWebStats.ps1.
    
    
SORTIES
    None. IISWebStats.ps1 does not generate any output.
    
    
NOTES
    
    
        To be valid, the log file format should be in text, and data should
        be separated by spaces. No other format can be accepted.
        
        First, when the script is looking for log files, it read first line
        of each log file and, in 50 first characters, looks for:
        "#Software: Microsoft Internet Information Services"
        
        If the script does not find this string, it does not consider the
        log file as an IIS valid log file.
        
        Secondly, to determine how to find the appropriate content, it read
        each line, then it need to find an header line containing list of
        fields or columns starting by "#Fields:" and following by columns
        titles. This header line should be placed before data line to let
        the script analyze logs.
        
        Used titles are "date", "cs-uri-stem", "cs-username", "c-ip" and
        "s-port". If all these fields are not in the log file the script
        will no be able to analyze.
        Theses fields or columns in the file can be in any order: the data
        should simply be in the same order than the headers.
    
    -------------------------- EXEMPLE 1 --------------------------
    
    PS C:\>.\IISWebStats.ps1
    
    Process on ALL default IIS Web log files on the local server.
    
    
    
    
    -------------------------- EXEMPLE 2 --------------------------
    
    PS C:\>.\IISWebStats.ps1 -SinceLast 2
    
    Process on last 2 months default IIS Web log files on the local server.
    
    
    
    
    -------------------------- EXEMPLE 3 --------------------------
    
    PS C:\>.\IISWebStats.ps1 FTP
    
    Process on ALL default IIS FTP log files on the local server.
    
    
    
    
    -------------------------- EXEMPLE 4 --------------------------
    
    PS C:\>.\IISWebStats.ps1 C:\Temp\LogFiles
    
    Process on ALL *.log files in C:\Temp\Logfiles directory on the local server.
    
    
    
    
    -------------------------- EXEMPLE 5 --------------------------
    
    PS C:\>.\IISWebStats.ps1 C:\Temp\LogFiles\20181225.txt
    
    Process on C:\Temp\LogFiles\20181225.txt log file only on the local server.
    
    
    
    
    
LIENS CONNEXES

